Michel Beaubien

1299 Huron St. London, Ontario | Phone: 226-376-4696 | michelBeaubien@hotmail.com www.michel-beaubien.com | linkedin.com/pub/michel-beaubien

Professional Summary

Three years of experience in all forms of web development, research and analysis, design, development, testing, and implementation of code and applications, as well as a variety of graphic design and artwork. I have been both a team leader and a team member, I know what it takes to get things done. I do not simply finish projects and push them aside, I constantly continue working on the websites.

Highlights

- Bilingual speaking & writing - french / english

- HTML 5

- CSS 3

- Javascript

-Code Igniter

- Live Portfolio Website

- Bootstrap

- Proofreading

- Quick Learner / Problem Solver

-Team player

Experience

Web Developer / Web Designer - www.tycreteconstruction.com

- Designed and coded this entire website myself

- Website was complete in a month, deadline was Dec. 20th

- All images are properly saved for web

Web Developer / Web Designer - Portfolio Website - www.michel-beaubien.com

- Designed website for clean user interaction

- PHP function for contact form

-Horizontal / verical parallax

Front-end developer - www.michel-beaubien.com/websites/Forrats/

-Team based project for small business website

-High organization / communication skills

-Used social media to plan and execute this site

Web Developer / Web Designer - www.beyondthebeach.ca & www.paradiseproperties.info

-Designed and developed these websites

-BTB was a re-model, kept in touch with constant client updates

-This was done for a returning client

Web Developer / Web Designer - www.justeventzz.com

-New web developer for a client

-Slowly re-designing the entire website

-Constant connections with client

10 / 2014 - Present

London, Ontario

London, Ontario

10 / 2014 - Present

01 / 2015 - 4 / 2015

London, Ontario

10 / 2014 - Present

London, Ontario

12 / 2015 - Present

London, Ontario

Education

Interactive Media Design & Production 2013 - 2015

Fanshawe College London, Ontario

Interactive Media Specialist 2015 - Present

Fanshawe College London, Ontario

Additional Information

Motivated and hard working web developer with the ability to create websites from concept to completion. My digital experience is complimented by my design and illustration skills.